Guide to the Bob Holman Audio/Video Poetry Collection 1977-2002 MSS.128
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: WNYC-TV "Poetry Spots", 1985-1992
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Spots IV, Undated; ID: 128.0182 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0182)
    - Poetry Spots - Season IV - Air, Undated; ID: 128.0183 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0183)
    - Poetry Spots Promo Pitch Pledge, 1992; ID: 128.0184 (Box 8, Media ID: 128.0184)
    - Poetry Season I, Undated; ID: 128.0185 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0185)
    - Poetry Season II, Undated; ID: 128.0186 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0186)
    - Poetry Spots 1/2 Hr. Compilation #1, Undated; ID: 128.0187 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0187)
    - Poetry Spots IV Compilation Reel, 1993; ID: 128.0188 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0188)
    - Poetry Spots / Chinese Cucumbers, Undated; ID: 128.0189 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0189)
    - The Great American Roller Coaster Poem - Rough Cut, Undated; ID: 128.0190 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0190)
    - The Great American Roller Coaster Poem - Final Edit, Undated; ID: 128.0191 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0191)
    - A Deed Without a Name - In Progress, Undated; ID: 128.0192 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0192)
    - Rough Cut of a Mike Tyler Poem "The 80s, A Toad", 1993; ID: 128.0193 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0193)
    - Edwin Torres in Two Videos By Kristine Diekman, Undated; ID: 128.0194 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0194)
    - Rogue Transmissions, 1993; ID: 128.0195 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0195)
    - The Hoover Poem - Laurie Carlos, Undated; ID: 128.0196 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0196)
    - [1]-- Mommie's Coming Back [2]-- Yoing, [1994]; ID: 128.0197A (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0197A)
    - Yoing, [1994]; ID: 128.0198A (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0198A)
    - Poetry Spots; Beatty Outtakes, Undated; ID: 128.0199 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0199)
    - Poetry Spots III "2 Black Men and a Baby On The Way"; Paul Beatty, 1992; ID: 128.0200 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0200)
    - "The Foxes Manifesto"; Kurt Larkin, Undated; ID: 128.0201 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0201)
    - "Chinese Cucumbers"; a poetry video by Kurt Heintz, 1994; ID: 128.0202 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0202)
      Format: Betacam SP
    - Dennis Downey Videos - 5 Video Pieces, Undated; ID: 128.0203 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0203)
    - Japan Men, 1989; ID: 128.0204 (Box 9, Media ID: 128.0204)
    - An Uncool Yul, 1992; ID: 128.0205 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0205)
      Format: 3/4 in. Umatic SP
    - Poetry Compilation Reel IV, Undated; ID: 128.0206 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0206)
    - Poetry Comp IV, Undated; ID: 128.0207 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0207)
    - Poetry Spots V - Compliation Reel, 1994; ID: 128.0208 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0208)
    - Poetry Spots V - Compliation Reel, 1994; ID: 128.0209 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0209)
    - Poetry Spots - Various Cuts, Undated; ID: 128.0210 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0210)
    - Poetry Spots V; Compilation Air Master, Undated; ID: 128.0211 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0211)
    - Poetry Spots V; Compilation Air Master, Undated; ID: 128.0212 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0212)
    - Poetry Spots V; Compilation Air Master, Undated; ID: 128.0213 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0213)
    - Poetry Spots VI Compilation Reel, 1995; ID: 128.0214 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0214)
    - Poetry Spots Season 6, Undated; ID: 128.0215 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0215)
    - Poetry Spots Season 6, Undated; ID: 128.0216 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0216)
    - An American Dream; A film by Andrea Kirsch, 1987; ID: 128.0217A (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0217A)
    - Treadwinds for Poetry Spots, 1992; ID: 128.0218 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0218)
      Format: 1 in.
    - Counting - Lisa Buscami, Undated; ID: 128.0219 (Box 10, Media ID: 128.0219)
    - Chinese Cucumbers - Patricia Smith, Undated; ID: 128.0220 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0220)
    - Poetry Spots III Compilation, Undated; ID: 128.0221 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0221)
    - Poetry Spots V Compilation Uncensored, 1994; ID: 128.0222 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0222)
    - Poetry Spots V; Various Cuts 1-9, 1994; ID: 128.0223 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0223)
    - Poetry Spots Season V Compilation, Undated; ID: 128.0224 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0224)
    - Poetry Spots V Air Master Various 1-9, 1994; ID: 128.0225 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0225)
    - Poetry Spots V Compilation, Undated; ID: 128.0226 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0226)
    - Poetry Spots V - Various Cuts Air Master, 1994; ID: 128.0227 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0227)
    - Poetry Spots VI Compilation Reel, Undated; ID: 128.0228 (Box 11, Media ID: 128.0228)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III Tape 1, [1991]; ID: 128.0229 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0229)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III Tape 2, 1991; ID: 128.0230 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0230)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III Tape 3, 1991; ID: 128.0231 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0231)
    - Paul Beatty; Poetry Spots III Tape 4, 1991; ID: 128.0232 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0232)
    - The Law is in the Seed - Kahnawake Shoot Tape #3, 1991; ID: 128.0233 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0233)
    - The Law is in the Seed - Billy Two Rivers #4, 1991; ID: 128.0234 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0234)
    - The Law is in the Seed - Final Edit Without Credits, 1991; ID: 128.0235 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0235)
    - The Law is in the Seed - Final Edit Dub With Credits, 1991; ID: 128.0236 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0236)
    - Poetry Spots - "So How Was Your Day" Tape #1, 1991; ID: 128.0237 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0237)
    - Poetry Spots - "So How Was Your Day" Tape #2, 1991; ID: 128.0238 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0238)
    - John Ash Poem - Edit Master, 1991; ID: 128.0239 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0239)
    - "You Startin' Wif Me"; A Tracie Morris Poem, 1991; ID: 128.0240 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0240)
    - "Nostalgia"; Laura Ciporen, 1991; ID: 128.0241 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0241)
    - Poetry Spot: "Bacalaitos y Fireworks", 1992; ID: 128.0242 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0242)
    - "A Child's Guide to Parenthood"; Laura Ciporen, [1991]; ID: 128.0243 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0243)
    - Treadwinds, [1994]; ID: 128.0244 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0244)
    - "Just Another Day"; Sandy Esteves, 1992; ID: 128.0245 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0245)
    - Alex Jacobs Outside Interview Tape #2, 1991; ID: 128.0246 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0246)
    - "Eternity"; Dave Henderson, Undated; ID: 128.0247A (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0247A)
    - "Charlie" - Short Version, 1991; ID: 128.0248 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0248)
    - Poetry Spot Opening - Season II Compilation, 1991; ID: 128.0249 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0249)
    - Poetry Spots III; Compilation Opening Sequence, 1993; ID: 128.0250 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0250)
    - Poetry Spots III - Padua, Sneed, Blumerzack, Undated; ID: 128.0251 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0251)
    - Poetry Spots Season III - Sample Reel, 1991; ID: 128.0252 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0252)
    - Poetry Spots Season 5 - Intro and Credits, Undated; ID: 128.0253 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0253)
    - Poetry Membership Spot With Bob Holman, 1992; ID: 128.0254 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0254)
    - Poetry Rap Reel 2, 1992; ID: 128.0255 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0255)
    - Arlene Gottfried Photos for Lois Griffith Poem, 1991; ID: 128.0256 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0256)
    - Dub Photos by Arlene Gottfried, Undated; ID: 128.0257 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0257)
    - Arlene Gottfried Shoot: El Barrio Tape 1, 1991; ID: 128.0258 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0258)
    - Arlene Gottfried Shoot: El Barrio Tape 2, 1991; ID: 128.0259 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0259)
    - Poetry Videos - Mark Ameen Tape #12, 1989; ID: 128.0260A (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0260A)
    - Poetry Videos - Mark Ameen Tape #14, 1989; ID: 128.0261 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0261)
    - Video Poetry: Deaf Poets Tape 2A, 1989; ID: 128.0262 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0262)
    - Tape #6; Show 104 - PS 61: Classrooms, Tour of School, 1990; ID: 128.0263 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0263)
    - Miguel Pinero Stills - B Tape, Undated; ID: 128.0264 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0264)
    - Nuyorican Poets Café - Rough Cut II, 1990; ID: 128.0265 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0265)
    - Transformations, Undated; ID: 128.0266 (Box 12, Media ID: 128.0266)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel Season I, [1990], 1994(Dub date?); ID: 128.0267 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0267)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel Season II - Part 1, 1991, 1994(Dub date?); ID: 128.0268 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0268)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel Season II - Part 2, 1991, 1994(Dub date?); ID: 128.0269 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0269)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Reel Season III, [1992], 1994(Dub date?); ID: 128.0270 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0270)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Season IV, 1993, 1994(Dub date?); ID: 128.0271 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0271)
    - Poetry Spots - Compilation Season IV - DUB, 1993, 1994(Dub date?); ID: 128.0272 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0272)
    - Poetry Spots V - Compilation Reel, 1994, 1994(Dub date?); ID: 128.0273 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0273)
    - Poetry Spots V - Compilation Reel, 1994, 1994(Dub date?); ID: 128.0274 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0274)
    - Latin Empire - Dub Master B Roll, 1990; ID: 128.0275 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0275)
    - Poetry Spots; Latin Empire - B Roll [Credit] Footage, 1990; ID: 128.0276 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0276)
    - Poetry Spot 5, Undated; ID: 128.0277 (Box 13, Media ID: 128.0277)
- Series III: "United States of Poetry", 1996
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - "Lost Planet; USOP; Peter Cook 'Hero Take' ", Undated (Media ID: 128.1014)
      Duration: [00:08:30]
      Original Format: VHS
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - U.S. Of Poetry/AMIC "The Land and the People" Episode #101, 1995; ID: 128.0278 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0278)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1 - The Land & The People, [1995]; ID: 128.0279 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0279)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1 - The Land & The People, 1995; ID: 128.0280 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0280)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1, 1995; ID: 128.0281 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0281)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1 - Rough Cut, 1995; ID: 128.0282 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0282)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 1 - Images/ Selects, [1995]; ID: 128.0283 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0283)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 2 - A Day in the Life, 1995; ID: 128.0284 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0284)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 2 - A Day in the Life, 1995; ID: 128.0285 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0285)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 2 - Early, 1995; ID: 128.0286 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0286)
    - U.S. Of Poetry/AMIC "The American Dream" Episode #103, 1995; ID: 128.0287 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0287)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3 - The American Dream, [1995]; ID: 128.0288 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0288)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3 - The American Dream, [1995]; ID: 128.0289 (Box 14, Media ID: 128.0289)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3, 1995; ID: 128.0290 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0290)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3 - The American Dream, 1995; ID: 128.0291 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0291)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 3 - The American Dream, 1995; ID: 128.0292 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0292)
    - U.S. Of Poetry/AMIC "Love and Sex" Episode #104, 1995; ID: 128.0293 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0293)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 4 - Love & Sex, [1995]; ID: 128.0294 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0294)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 4 - Love & Sex, 1995; ID: 128.0295 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0295)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show #4, 1995; ID: 128.0296 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0296)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 4 - Love & Sex, 1995; ID: 128.0297 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0297)
    - U.S. Of Poetry/AMIC "The Word" Episode #105, 1995; ID: 128.0298 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0298)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 5 - The Word, 1995; ID: 128.0299 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0299)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 5 - The Word, [1995]; ID: 128.0300 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0300)
    - The United States of Poetry; Show 5 - The Word, 1995; ID: 128.0301 (Box 15, Media ID: 128.0301)
    - The United States of Poetry; Shows 1,2,3, [1995]; ID: 128.0302 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0302)
    - The United States of Poetry; Shows 1,2,3, [1995]; ID: 128.0303 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0303)
    - The United States of Poetry; Shows 4, 5, [1995]; ID: 128.0304 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0304)
    - USOP 4 & 5, [1995]; ID: 128.0305 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0305)
    - The United States of Poetry: 4) Love and Sex, 5) The Word, [1995]; ID: 128.0306 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0306)
    - USOP: Eps. 101 The Land and the People, Eps. 102 A Day in the Life, Eps. 103 The American Dream, [1997]; ID: 128.0307A (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0307A)
    - United States of Poetry Episode #104 "Love & Sex" Episode #105 "The Word", Undated; ID: 128.0308 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0308)
    - United States of Poetry - Sampler, [1995]; ID: 128.0309 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0309)
    - United States of Poetry - Sampler, [1995]; ID: 128.0310 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0310)
    - United States of Poetry - Sampler, [1995]; ID: 128.0311 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0311)
    - United States of Poetry; National Market, 1996; ID: 128.0312 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0312)
    - The United States of Poetry; Programs One - Three, 1996; ID: 128.0313 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0313)
    - The United States of Poetry; Programs Four - Five, 1996; ID: 128.0314 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0314)
    - The US of Poetry #27; CR# A76-A79, A81-A82, 1994; ID: 128.0315 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0315)
    - Lost Planet; USOP; Peter Cook "Hero Take", Undated; ID: 128.0316 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0316)
    - Various Poets; United States of Poetry #104 "Love and Sex", 1996; ID: 128.0317 (Box 16, Media ID: 128.0317)
- Series IV: Mouth Almighty/ Mercury Records, 1996-1999
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - Ballad of the Skeletons, Undated (Media ID: 128.0990)
      Duration: 00:05:00
    - Maggie Estep "Hey Baby" 2:22 R-rated, Undated (Media ID: 128.0984)
    - Maggie Estep "EPK", Undated (Media ID: 128.0987)
      Duration: 00:06:00
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - SF National Poetry Slam Selects, 1993; ID: 128.0318 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0318)
    - Maggie Estep; "Hey Baby" - Rough Cut, 1994; ID: 128.0319 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0319)
    - [1]--"Hey Baby" Video Mix (Clean) [2]-- "Hey Baby" LP MIX (Clean) [3]-- "Hey Baby" Video Mix (Uncensored), 1994; ID: 128.0320A (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0320A)
    - Maggie Estep; "Hey Baby" - R-Rated, [1994]; ID: 128.0321 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0321)
    - Maggie Estep; "Hey Baby" - Version #1 (R-Rated) and Version #3 (G-Rated), [1994]; ID: 128.0322 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0322)
    - Maggie Estep; "EPK", Undated; ID: 128.0323 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0323)
    - Maggie Estep; "EPK", Undated; ID: 128.0324 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0324)
    - Maggie Estep; "EPK", Undated; ID: 128.0325 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0325)
    - The Maggie Estep Combo "EPK/ Arsenio Hall Show", [1994]; ID: 128.0326 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0326)
    - The Maggie Estep Combo "EPK/ Arsenio Hall Show", [1994]; ID: 128.0327 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0327)
    - The Maggie Estep Combo "EPK/ Arsenio Hall Show", [1994]; ID: 128.0328 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0328)
    - Estep/ Arsenio, 1994; ID: 128.0329 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0329)
    - Maggie Estep; Normal Girl on MTV/ Jon Stewart, Undated; ID: 128.0330 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0330)
    - Maggie Estep; "Vicious" Final Cut - Three Versions, 1997; ID: 128.0331 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0331)
    - Maggie Estep; "Vicious" Rough Cut - Three Versions, 1997; ID: 128.0332 (Box 17, Media ID: 128.0332)
    - Sekou Sundiata; EPK, 1997; ID: 128.0333 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0333)
    - Sekou Sundiata; EPK, 1997; ID: 128.0334 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0334)
    - Sekou Sundiata; EPK, [1997]; ID: 128.0335 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0335)
    - Last Poets; Rap City, [ca. 1995]; ID: 128.0336 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0336)
    - Our Voices 95-18/Last Poets, 1995; ID: 128.0337 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0337)
    - Last Poets; "Sound FX", 1995; ID: 128.0338 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0338)
    - Last Poets 4/9/97 Edit, 1997; ID: 128.0339 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0339)
    - Beyond Life; Timothy Leary Lives, 1997; ID: 128.0340 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0340)
    - Allen Ginsberg w/ Paul McCartney, Philip Glass & Lenny Kaye; "Ballad of the Skeletons", 1997; ID: 128.0341 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0341)
    - Allen Ginsberg w/ Paul McCartney, Philip Glass & Lenny Kaye; "Ballad of the Skeletons", 1997; ID: 128.0342 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0342)
    - Allen Ginsberg w/ Paul McCartney, Philip Glass & Lenny Kaye; "Ballad of the Skeletons", 1997; ID: 128.0343 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0343)
    - Allen Ginsberg; "Ballad of the Skeletons", Undated; ID: 128.0344 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0344)
    - Allen Ginsberg; "Ballad of the Skeletons", 1996; ID: 128.0345 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0345)
    - Wammo Interview, Undated; ID: 128.0346 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0346)
    - Wammo Footage; Tapes 1 & 2, Undated; ID: 128.0347 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0347)
    - Wammo; "There Is Too Much Light In This Bar", 1997; ID: 128.0348 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0348)
    - Wammo; "Edit"; "There Is Too Much Light In This Bar", 1998; ID: 128.0349 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0349)
    - Mouth Almighty Prod. Presentaion 97, [1997]; ID: 128.0350 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0350)
    - Mercury Records/ Mouth Almighty Presentation, [1997]; ID: 128.0351 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0351)
    - Mouth Almighty 1997 PGD Presentation, ID: 128.0352 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0352)
    - Mouth Almighty PGD Presentation 97, 1997; ID: 128.0353 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0353)
    - Mouth Almighty 8/13/96, 1996; ID: 128.0354 (Box 18, Media ID: 128.0354)
- Series V: Grassroots Poetry Videos, 1988-2001
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - "Exchange Place" written by Reggie Gaines, Undated (Media ID: 128.0993)
      Duration: 00:09:00
    - "Psychic Defense" Training for Ex-Lovers, Undated (Media ID: 128.0996)
    - The Poetry Video Learning Project: "Rooms of Our Lives", Undated (Media ID: 128.0999)
      Duration: 00:14:00
    - Doug Knott's Small Dogs Bark 3, Undated (Media ID: 128.1002)
    - "Flying Words Project: 'If You Want It' ", 1989 (Media ID: 128.1017)
      Duration: [00:08:00]
    - "Video Poetry," Curated by George Fifield, June - September 1994 (Media ID: 128.1020)
      Duration: [00:43:00]
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Reggie Gaines; "Exchange Place", Undated; ID: 128.0355 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0355)
    - Reggie Gaines; "Exchange Place", Undated; ID: 128.0356 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0356)
    - "Cab"; R. Gaines, Undated; ID: 128.0357 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0357)
    - "Anavision"; Amy Halloran, 1989; ID: 128.0358 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0358)
    - "Pledge"; Lee Ann Brown, 1990; ID: 128.0359 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0359)
    - Lisa Buscani; "Live at the Green Mill", Undated; ID: 128.0360 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0360)
    - Bob Carroll; [1]-- Four Works [2]-- Impossible Theater "I Buy Shoes", [1]--1981 [2]--1986; ID: 128.0361 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0361)
    - [1]-- Bob Carroll; "Salmon Show" [2]-- KPFA Benefit, Undated; ID: 128.0362 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0362)
    - Dead Bob's Birthday Bash 7/6/88, 1988; ID: 128.0363 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0363)
    - Dead Bob's Birthday Bash 7/6/88, 1988; ID: 128.0364 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0364)
    - Todd Colby Reading Poems, Undated; ID: 128.0365 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0365)
    - Alvin Eng; "Selected Compilation", [1&2]--1990 [3]--1989 [4]--1993; ID: 128.0366 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0366)
    - Pat Smith: Selected Readings, 1990-91, 1991; ID: 128.0367 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0367)
    - Holly Hughes: "World Without End", 1989; ID: 128.0368 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0368)
    - Dean Hacker's Poetry For Bob Holman, Undated; ID: 128.0369 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0369)
    - Larry Goodell: "Colores", 1990; ID: 128.0370 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0370)
    - Vivien Bittencourt/ Vincent Katz - April Dark Rain 1987, ID: 128.0371 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0371)
    - Two Of Kenneth Koch's "One Thousand Avante-Garde Plays", 1990; ID: 128.0372 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0372)
    - Flying Words Project: "If You Want It", 1989; ID: 128.0373 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0373)
    - Fanny Howe: "Light Words To Rumi Over Time", Undated; ID: 128.0374 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0374)
    - Fanny Howe: "Be Again", Undated; ID: 128.0375 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0375)
    - Fanny Howe & John Gianvito: "What Nobody Saw", Undated; ID: 128.0376 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0376)
    - Elmer Lang, Undated; ID: 128.0377 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0377)
    - Deacon Lunchbox 2/20/91, 1991; ID: 128.0378 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0378)
    - "Eileen Myles for President", 1992; ID: 128.0379 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0379)
    - Lisa Siegel & Kendrick Jarret: "Bicycle Days", Undated; ID: 128.0380 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0380)
    - Art Performance, 1989; ID: 128.0381A (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0381A)
    - PBS Innovations Series: The Future Is Now - Eliot Soloway Segment, 1992 (Aired); ID: 128.0382 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0382)
    - Poet Laundromat, 1988; ID: 128.0383 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0383)
    - Mexico City Blues: A Reading With Live Music, 1988; ID: 128.0384 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0384)
    - Future of Poetry Party at Electronic Café International, 6/30/19??; ID: 128.0385 (Box 19, Media ID: 128.0385)
    - Elec. Cafe, Undated; ID: 128.0386 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0386)
    - "Words Against War"; San Francisco, 1/15/91, 1991; ID: 128.0387A (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0387A)
    - Bad Words: 8 Excerpts, Undated; ID: 128.0388 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0388)
    - Zero-TV, Undated; ID: 128.0389 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0389)
    - Best of RSPT Live, 1990; ID: 128.0390 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0390)
    - Quick Cuts, 1989; ID: 128.0391 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0391)
    - [1]-- Before the War [2]-- California One, 1990; ID: 128.0392 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0392)
    - Dennis Moritz: "Something To Hold On To…", Undated; ID: 128.0393 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0393)
    - Neill Bogan: "The Dead Could Not Afford Heaven", [1991]; ID: 128.0394 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0394)
    - "The Dead Could Not Afford Heaven" Part One, 1991; ID: 128.0395 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0395)
    - Alive From Off Center; Press Preview 1990, ID: 128.0396 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0396)
    - Lord Buckley, Undated; ID: 128.0397 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0397)
    - Eight Million: Child & Mori, 1991; ID: 128.0398 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0398)
    - History & Memory for Akiko Takashige, 1991; ID: 128.0399 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0399)
    - Elizabeth Streb / Ringside - Promo Video, 1989-1990; ID: 128.0400 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0400)
    - Basil King / Dave Geary, Undated; ID: 128.0401 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0401)
    - "Corporation With a Movie Camera", 1992; ID: 128.0402 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0402)
    - Dreams Inside and Out, 1982-1989 (Filmed); ID: 128.0403A (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0403A)
    - Behind Every Great Man Is A Thin Boy Waiting To Get Out, 1991; ID: 128.0404 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0404)
    - Night of the Living Sidemen, Undated; ID: 128.0405A (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0405A)
    - Psychic Defense Training For Ex Lovers, Undated; ID: 128.0406A (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0406A)
    - Psychic Defense Training For Ex Lovers, Undated; ID: 128.0407 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0407)
    - Hopatcong Arrival, 1993; ID: 128.0408 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0408)
    - Jim Cohn: [1]--"Prarie Falcon" [2]-- "Atonement", Undated; ID: 128.0409 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0409)
    - "Rooms of Our Own" - Three Shows, Undated; ID: 128.0410 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0410)
    - Poetry Vignettes - Bob Borgatti/ Paul Lamont, Undated; ID: 128.0411 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0411)
    - Vintage Swat's Big Horror Poetry Series 1987-90, 1987-1990; ID: 128.0412 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0412)
    - "From The Fringe": a poetry spot by Mickey Z, 1993; ID: 128.0413 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0413)
    - Dana Gioia Poetry Reading, 1993; ID: 128.0414 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0414)
    - Brooke Berman - Three Text Video(s), Undated; ID: 128.0415 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0415)
    - Consumer Response, 1991; ID: 128.0416 (Box 20, Media ID: 128.0416)